John Patrick Resurreccion

Software Developer

 $+63\ 956\ 672\ 3445 \cdot patrickjohn.resurreccion 18@gmail.com \cdot https://www.linkedin.com/in/john-patrick-resurreccion-5b5314213/ \cdot https://patjohntrick.vercel.app/ Catanauan, Quezon$

SUMMARY

Experienced in building web apps and mobile applications using the power of React Technology. Experienced in creating multiple features based on the clients requirements. Participated in sprint planning, daily stand ups, demo and retrospective. Has a strong value of time and dedication for assigned tickets in a sprint. Participated also on collaboration between Designers, QA's and Backend Developers to ensure the productivity in building desired output for the project.

SKILLS / KEY COMPETENCIES

Web Front End Programming Testing and Maintenance Mobile App Development Reporting and presenting with client Critical thinking skills Excellent communication skills Strong interpersonal skills Proactive and self-motivated Database Programming

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Zeniark Philippines Consulting Corp React Developer

April 2023 - Present

 $Technologies - Typescript \cdot ReactJS \cdot NextJS \cdot Zod/Yup \cdot RTK \ Query \cdot TanStack \cdot Ant \ Design \cdot Mantine \ Ultimate the properties of th$

- Created responsive ReactJS and/or NextJS web components with Ant Design to provide better user interface and interaction
- Developed UI based on the design from Figma and/or Sketch including multiple features based on the tasks requirements for websites and/or web apps
- Coordination with the Backend, QA, fellow Front End, Team Lead and Project Manager to ensure the productive work
- Participated DSM's, sprint planning, ticket assigning, retrospective and more
- Perform code review and knowledge transfer with the team
- Integrate API. Perform HTTP requests such as GET, POST, PATCH, PUT and DELETE using RTK Query and TanStack Query

ISBX Philippines, Inc Fullstack Developer

Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

- $Technologies Typescript \cdot ReactJS/React\ Native \cdot NextJS \cdot NestJS \cdot PostgreSQL \cdot Formik \cdot Yup \cdot Material\ UI$
 - Developed Web Application and Mobile Application for multiple clients
 - Participated DSM's, sprint planning, ticket assigning, retrospective and more
 - Created Unit Testing and End to End Testing using Jest to ensure each features and endpoints are working as expected
 - Created API to serve data to the client side using NestJS as backend and PostgreSQL as database
 - Added different validations based on each endpoints and data
 - Integrate different third party packages to achieve specific goals based on the requirements

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

STI College Lucena

BS in Information Technology 2018 - 2022

Bondoc Peninsula Agricultural High School

2012 - 2018

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

EPAS President

Bondoc Peninsula Agricultural High School